Narrator: 1
A: I’m from China.
B: He’s Chinese.
Narrator: 2
A: I’m from Spain.
B: She’s Spanish.
Narrator: 3
A: I’m from Japan.
B: He’s Japanese.
Narrator: 4
A: I’m from Switzerland.
B: She’s Swiss.
Narrator: 5
A: I’m from the USA.
B: He’s American.
Narrator: 6
A: I’m from Italy.
B: She’s Italian.
Narrator: 7
A: I’m from Germany.
B: He’s German.
Narrator: 8
A: I’m from Mexico.
B: She’s Mexican.
Narrator: 9
A: I’m from England.
B: He’s English.
Narrator: 10
A: I’m from Türkiye.
B: She’s Turkish.
Narrator: 11
A: I’m from Poland.
B: He’s Polish.
Narrator: 12
A: I’m from Egypt.
B: She’s Egyptian.
Narrator: 13
A: I’m from Brazil.
B: He’s Brazilian.
Narrator: 14
A: I’m from France.
B: She’s French.
Narrator: 15
A: I’m from Russia.
B: He’s Russian.
Narrator: 16
A: I’m from the UK.
B: She’s British.
Narrator: 17
A: I’m from Nigeria.
B: He’s Nigerian.